{
    "subject": "resource/2011\u201312_St._Louis_Blues_season",
    "predicate": "property/birthplace",
    "object": "resource/Newmarket,_Ontario",
    "human_readable": "The birthplace of the 2011-12 St. Louis Blues season is Newmarket, Ontario.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9044130444526672,
            "question": "What city in Ontario was the starting point for the 2011-12 St. Louis Blues season?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8213744163513184,
            "question": "What year did the 2011-12 St. Louis Blues season commence?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8170843720436096,
            "question": "Where did the 2011-12 St. Louis Blues season originate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7984392642974854,
            "question": "In which province did the 2011-12 St. Louis Blues season begin?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7316939830780029,
            "question": "Is there a historical connection between Newmarket and the St. Louis Blues?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6893279552459717,
            "question": "Was Newmarket, Ontario the birthplace of any famous athletes?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.43131494522094727,
            "question": "Is Newmarket, Ontario associated with a professional sports team?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22684639692306519,
            "question": "Which NHL team is connected to Newmarket, Ontario?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.20667672157287598,
            "question": "Can you name a hockey team associated with Newmarket, Ontario?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.19367796182632446,
            "question": "What type of professional sports team originated in Newmarket, Ontario?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The birthplace of the 2011-12 St. Louis Blues season is Newmarket, Ontario.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7311_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name a hockey team associated with Newmarket, Ontario?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7311_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which NHL team is connected to Newmarket, Ontario?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7311_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Newmarket, Ontario associated with a professional sports team?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7311_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7311_121.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7311_126.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7311_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7311_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7311_72.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7311_8.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7311_91.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7311_96.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7311_97.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7311_99.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\nThe documents provided mention players from the St. Louis Blues and details about their careers and backgrounds, but they don't state that Newmarket, Ontario, was the birthplace of the team's 2011-12 season.  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here's the answer in JSON format:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation:\n\nThe documents mention Jordan Binnington as a player for the St. Louis Blues and his birthplace as Richmond Hill, Ontario. However, there is no information about the birthplace of the 2011-12 St. Louis Blues season itself.\n\nIn fact, the text refers to Jordan Binnington's birthplace, not the birthplace of the team or its season. The only mention of Newmarket is in relation to a player named McKee, who played for the Lincoln Stars and was from Newmarket, ON."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n```\n\nExplanation:\nThe provided documents do not contain any information about the birthplace of the 2011-12 St. Louis Blues season or related to Newmarket, Ontario. The document mentioning a connection to Ontario is about Jordan Binnington's place of birth, but it does not relate to the team's roster or the 2011-2012 season starting in Newmarket, Ontario."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"no\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 0,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}